modelful.com 2008-12-16

# ModelFul

Modelful.com is dedicated to safeguarding your online privacy. The following explains how your information will be treated as you make use of our products and services. __ **Your Information**    
Modelful.com draws a distinction between information that is provided when registering and information that is used for making your web pages through modelful.com

**Personal Information**   
Personal information is defined as any information entered when registering or using services obtained through our Web site, information you provide as part of registration for one of our promotional campaign or any other information collected about you on our Web site (such as how long you spend on the Web site, what you look at on the Web site, etc.) We at modelful.com constantly strive to provide useful products and services based on the content of our site and on related subjects of matter. 

**Cookies**  
To enhance your visit with personalized services, modelful.com makes use of cookie technology. A cookie is a small file that is assigned to a user when he or she registers on a Web site. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, nor are they shared with our partners and vendors. We use cookie technology to track the way in which clients use the site so that we can provide them with content that caters to their needs. This includes participation in our promotional and other free services to clients. We also use cookies to make your visit more convenient by saving your password or registration so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

**IP Address** ****  
IP addresses are unique to each computer, and they are used to identify senders and receivers information over the Internet. Modelful.com uses your computer's IP address to administer our Web site to verify your identity and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. 

**Contests and Surveys** ****  
Modelful.com occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. This information is shared with advertisers and other stakeholders on an aggregate basis unless you otherwise consent. Individual user information is not released without your consent.

    **A Word about Security** ****  
At modelful.com, we are committed to maintaining a secured environment to store and receive your personal information. All of the information transmitted to modelful.com is stored safely and securely behind our firewall. A firewall is a buffer that isolates our network from the Internet. 

  At modelful.com, we constantly monitor our Web security to protect your information. Once your information is received at modelful.com, access to your information is limited. Each employee is provided with a copy of this document so that they are aware of our privacy practices. 

Modelful.com works closely with our partners to ensure your privacy, however, we are not responsible for the privacy policy or content of our partners' Web sites or of third-party vendors. 

Unless otherwise noted herein we will not disclose any of your personal information to third parties, except when we have your permission or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

**Changing and Editing Your Information** ****  
You, as a user, can change or edit your personal information at any time. This procedure is accomplished by choosing to edit your profile account information or registration information once logged in on our Web site. If you have any difficulties with, or questions about the modification of personal information, please contact at 

_[info@modelful.com](mailto:info@modelful.com)_

. ****

**Conclusion**  
Thank you for taking the time to educate yourself about the ways in which modelful.com collects, uses, and stores the information that you provide. We recommend that you also read our Terms and Conditions of Service and Use since it provides more information about modelful.com policies. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and security statement, please email _[info@modelful.com](mailto:info@modelful.com)_. Please revisit this site on occasions to make sure that you have viewed the most recent version of the privacy policy and security statement. Modelful.com reserves the right to change any of the information listed on this document and will notify users of any changes by posting the new version of this document to the site at the Privacy Policy & Security Statement link.
